<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>Află totul despre moda masculină</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 17:44:17 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 17:44:17 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reguli majore pentru costum</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Fiecare bărbat ar trebui să aibă un costum în garderoba lui. Indiferent dacă îl purtați la ocazii speciale sau zilnic, un costum va fi întotdeauna esențial. Cu toate acestea, ca toate lucrurile, există anumite reguli pe care trebuie să le urmați întotdeauna. În acest articol vă vom prezenta câteva reguli esențiale pe care trebuie să le îndeplinească un costum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;tipuri-de-costume&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Tipuri de costume&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;fit-ul-costumelor&quot;&gt;Fit-ul costumelor&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Primul lucru pe care trebuie să îl iei în considerare este să vezi ce costum ți se potrivește cel mai bine. Cu opțiunile de &lt;i&gt;skinny&lt;/i&gt; sau &lt;i&gt;slim&lt;/i&gt;, cele mai populare acum, trebuie să știi care îți este cel mai potrivit. Înțelegerea diferenței dintre cele două te va ajuta să faci alegerea potrivită.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;slim-fit&quot;&gt;Slim Fit&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cel mai popular și potrivit pentru majoritatea bărbaților este costumul slim fit. Cu o croială slim de la umeri până la brâu, sacoul unui costum slim va oferi un mare confort. Acest tip de costum este ideal pentru bărbații cu corpul atletic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;skinny-fit&quot;&gt;Skinny Fit&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Un costum mai strâmt față de cel slim este cel skinny. Strâmt în jurul umerilor și adus mai mult în jurul taliei, acest tip de costum este conceput pentru bărbații înalți și slabi. Costumele skinny sunt potrivite pentru evenimentele oficiale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;detaliile-contează&quot;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Detaliile contează&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Un pas important este atenția la detalii. Nu vrei să te simți inconfortabil și nici nu vrei să te îneci în țesături. De la brațe și picioare până la piept, fii sigur că îți cunoști mărimile. Indiferent dacă ai umerii largi sau nu, este important să încerci mai întâi sacoul. Dacă ești între mărimi și nu găsești niciodată costumul potrivit este bine să apelezi la un croitor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;manșetele&quot;&gt;Manșetele&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unii bărbați au mâinile mai lungi decât alții, deci este greu să determini pe deplin ce se poate face cu manșetele tale dacă ai brațe lungi. Ideal este ca manșeta să fie mai lungă cu aproximativ un centimentru față de mânecile sacoului. Dacă trebuie să scurtați brațele sau să cumpărați o cămașă mai mare pentru a compensa mânecile, atunci este recomandat să consulați un croitor pentru o opinie profesională.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../assets/images/cuffs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;alt text&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;lungimea-pantalonilor&quot;&gt;Lungimea pantalonilor&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pantalonii trebuie să ajungă până la gleznă. Când vă așezați, pantalonii tăi se vor ridica puțin, așa că pentru a nu se vedea pielea ai nevoie de o pereche de șosete lungi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../../../../assets/images/trousers.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;alt text&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/costum/2019/02/06/reguli-majore-costum.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/costum/2019/02/06/reguli-majore-costum.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>costum</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Powerful things you can do with the Markdown editor</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There are lots of powerful things you can do with the Markdown editor. If you’ve gotten pretty comfortable with writing in Markdown, then you may enjoy some more advanced tips about the types of things you can do with Markdown!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with the last post about the editor, you’ll want to be actually editing this post as you read it so that you can see all the Markdown code we’re using.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;special-formatting&quot;&gt;Special formatting&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As well as bold and italics, you can also use some other special formatting in Markdown when the need arises, for example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;del&gt;strike through&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;==highlight==&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;*escaped characters*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;writing-code-blocks&quot;&gt;Writing code blocks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two types of code elements which can be inserted in Markdown, the first is inline, and the other is block. Inline code is formatted by wrapping any word or words in back-ticks, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;like this&lt;/code&gt;. Larger snippets of code can be displayed across multiple lines using triple back ticks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;.my-link {
    text-decoration: underline;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to get really fancy, you can even add syntax highlighting using Rouge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/mediumish-theme-jekyll/assets/images/8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;walking&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;reference-lists&quot;&gt;Reference lists&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The quick brown jumped over the lazy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another way to insert links in markdown is using reference lists. You might want to use this style of linking to cite reference material in a Wikipedia-style. All of the links are listed at the end of the document, so you can maintain full separation between content and its source or reference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;full-html&quot;&gt;Full HTML&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the best part of Markdown is that you’re never limited to just Markdown. You can write HTML directly in the Markdown editor and it will just work as HTML usually does. No limits! Here’s a standard YouTube embed code as an example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe style=&quot;width:100%;&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Cniqsc9QfDo?rel=0&amp;amp;showinfo=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/tutorial/2018/06/12/powerful-things-markdown-editor.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/tutorial/2018/06/12/powerful-things-markdown-editor.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The first mass-produced book to deviate from a rectilinear format</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The first mass-produced book to deviate from a rectilinear format, at least in the United States, is thought to be this 1863 edition of Red Riding Hood, cut into the shape of the protagonist herself with the troublesome wolf curled at her feet. Produced by the Boston-based publisher Louis Prang, this is the first in their “Doll Series”, a set of five “die-cut” books, known also as shape books — the other titles being Robinson Crusoe, Goody Two-Shoes (also written by Red Riding Hood author Lydia Very), Cinderella, and King Winter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An 1868 Prang catalogue would later claim that such “books in the shape of a regular paper Doll… originated with us”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It would seem the claim could also extend to die cut books in general, as we can’t find anything sooner, but do let us know in the comments if you have further light to shed on this! Such books are, of course, still popular in children’s publishing today, though the die cutting is not now limited to mere outlines, as evidenced in a beautiful 2014 version of the same Little Red Riding Hood story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The die cut has also been employed in the non-juvenile sphere as well, a recent example being Jonathan Safran Foer’s ambitious Tree of Codes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for this particular rendition of Charles Perrault’s classic tale, the text and design is by Lydia Very (1823-1901), sister of Transcendentalist poet Jones Very. The gruesome ending of the original - which sees Little Red Riding Hood being gobbled up as well as her grandmother - is avoided here, the gore giving way to the less bloody aims of the morality tale, and the lesson that one should not disobey one’s mother.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/tutorial/2018/06/12/first-mass-produced.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/tutorial/2018/06/12/first-mass-produced.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Education must also train one for quick, resolute and effective thinking.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There are lots of powerful things you can do with the Markdown editor&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’ve gotten pretty comfortable with writing in Markdown, then you may enjoy some more advanced tips about the types of things you can do with Markdown!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with the last post about the editor, you’ll want to be actually editing this post as you read it so that you can see all the Markdown code we’re using.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;special-formatting&quot;&gt;Special formatting&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As well as bold and italics, you can also use some other special formatting in Markdown when the need arises, for example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;del&gt;strike through&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;==highlight==&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;*escaped characters*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;writing-code-blocks&quot;&gt;Writing code blocks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two types of code elements which can be inserted in Markdown, the first is inline, and the other is block. Inline code is formatted by wrapping any word or words in back-ticks, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;like this&lt;/code&gt;. Larger snippets of code can be displayed across multiple lines using triple back ticks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;.my-link {
    text-decoration: underline;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to get really fancy, you can even add syntax highlighting using Rouge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/mediumish-theme-jekyll/assets/images/8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;walking&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;reference-lists&quot;&gt;Reference lists&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The quick brown jumped over the lazy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another way to insert links in markdown is using reference lists. You might want to use this style of linking to cite reference material in a Wikipedia-style. All of the links are listed at the end of the document, so you can maintain full separation between content and its source or reference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;full-html&quot;&gt;Full HTML&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the best part of Markdown is that you’re never limited to just Markdown. You can write HTML directly in the Markdown editor and it will just work as HTML usually does. No limits! Here’s a standard YouTube embed code as an example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe style=&quot;width:100%;&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Cniqsc9QfDo?rel=0&amp;amp;showinfo=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/tutorial/2018/06/12/education.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/tutorial/2018/06/12/education.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Accumulated experience of social living</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The die cut has also been employed in the non-juvenile sphere as well, a recent example being Jonathan Safran Foer’s ambitious Tree of Codes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for this particular rendition of Charles Perrault’s classic tale, the text and design is by Lydia Very (1823-1901), sister of Transcendentalist poet Jones Very. The gruesome ending of the original - which sees Little Red Riding Hood being gobbled up as well as her grandmother - is avoided here, the gore giving way to the less bloody aims of the morality tale, and the lesson that one should not disobey one’s mother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first mass-produced book to deviate from a rectilinear format, at least in the United States, is thought to be this 1863 edition of Red Riding Hood, cut into the shape of the protagonist herself with the troublesome wolf curled at her feet. Produced by the Boston-based publisher Louis Prang, this is the first in their “Doll Series”, a set of five “die-cut” books, known also as shape books — the other titles being Robinson Crusoe, Goody Two-Shoes (also written by Red Riding Hood author Lydia Very), Cinderella, and King Winter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An 1868 Prang catalogue would later claim that such “books in the shape of a regular paper Doll… originated with us”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It would seem the claim could also extend to die cut books in general, as we can’t find anything sooner, but do let us know in the comments if you have further light to shed on this! Such books are, of course, still popular in children’s publishing today, though the die cutting is not now limited to mere outlines, as evidenced in a beautiful 2014 version of the same Little Red Riding Hood story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/tutorial/2018/06/12/acumulated-experience.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/tutorial/2018/06/12/acumulated-experience.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>About Bundler</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;gem install bundler&lt;/code&gt; installs the bundler gem through RubyGems. You only need to install it once - not every time you create a new Jekyll project. Here are some additional details:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;bundler&lt;/code&gt; is a gem that manages other Ruby gems. It makes sure your gems and gem versions are compatible, and that you have all necessary dependencies each gem requires.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Gemfile&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Gemfile.lock&lt;/code&gt; files inform &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Bundler&lt;/code&gt; about the gem requirements in your site. If your site doesn’t have these Gemfiles, you can omit &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;bundle exec&lt;/code&gt; and just &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;run jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;bundle exec jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Bundler&lt;/code&gt; uses the gems and versions as specified in &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Gemfile.lock&lt;/code&gt; to ensure your Jekyll site builds with no compatibility or dependency conflicts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information about how to use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Bundler&lt;/code&gt; in your Jekyll project, this tutorial should provide answers to the most common questions and explain how to get up and running quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/2018/05/12/about-bundler.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/2018/05/12/about-bundler.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is Jekyll</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;No more databases, comment moderation, or pesky updates to install-just your content. Markdown, Liquid, HTML &amp;amp; CSS go in. Static sites come out ready for deployment. Permalinks, categories, pages, posts, and custom layouts are all first-class citizens here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sick of dealing with hosting companies? GitHub Pages are powered by Jekyll, so you can easily deploy your site using GitHub for free-custom domain name and all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-jekyll&quot;&gt;What is Jekyll?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll is a simple, blog-aware, static site generator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You create your content as text files (Markdown), and organize them into folders. Then, you build the shell of your site using Liquid-enhanced HTML templates. Jekyll automatically stitches the content and templates together, generating a website made entirely of static assets, suitable for uploading to any server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll happens to be the engine behind GitHub Pages, so you can host your project’s Jekyll page/blog/website on GitHub’s servers for free.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/tutorial/2018/02/05/reguli-costum.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/tutorial/2018/02/05/reguli-costum.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>We all wait for summer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As I engage in the so-called “bull sessions” around and about the school, I too often find that most college men have a misconception of the purpose of education. Most of the “brethren” think that education should equip them with the proper instruments of exploitation so that they can forever trample over the masses. Still others think that education should furnish them with noble ends rather than means to an end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems to me that education has a two-fold function to perform in the life of man and in society: the one is utility and the other is culture. Education must enable a man to become more efficient, to achieve with increasing facility the ligitimate goals of his life.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/we-all-wait-for-summer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/we-all-wait-for-summer.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tree of Codes</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The first mass-produced book to deviate from a rectilinear format, at least in the United States, is thought to be this 1863 edition of Red Riding Hood, cut into the shape of the protagonist herself with the troublesome wolf curled at her feet. Produced by the Boston-based publisher Louis Prang, this is the first in their “Doll Series”, a set of five “die-cut” books, known also as shape books — the other titles being Robinson Crusoe, Goody Two-Shoes (also written by Red Riding Hood author Lydia Very), Cinderella, and King Winter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for this particular rendition of Charles Perrault’s classic tale, the text and design is by Lydia Very (1823-1901), sister of Transcendentalist poet Jones Very. The gruesome ending of the original — which sees Little Red Riding Hood being gobbled up as well as her grandmother — is avoided here, the gore giving way to the less bloody aims of the morality tale, and the lesson that one should not disobey one’s mother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It would seem the claim could also extend to die cut books in general, as we can’t find anything sooner, but do let us know in the comments if you have further light to shed on this! Such books are, of course, still popular in children’s publishing today, though the die cutting is not now limited to mere outlines, as evidenced in a beautiful 2014 version of the same Little Red Riding Hood story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An 1868 Prang catalogue would later claim that such “books in the shape of a regular paper Doll… originated with us”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The die cut has also been employed in the non-juvenile sphere as well, a recent example being Jonathan Safran Foer’s ambitious Tree of Codes.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/tree-of-codes.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/tree-of-codes.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Red Riding Hood</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The first mass-produced book to deviate from a rectilinear format, at least in the United States, is thought to be this 1863 edition of Red Riding Hood, cut into the shape of the protagonist herself with the troublesome wolf curled at her feet. Produced by the Boston-based publisher Louis Prang, this is the first in their “Doll Series”, a set of five “die-cut” books, known also as shape books — the other titles being Robinson Crusoe, Goody Two-Shoes (also written by Red Riding Hood author Lydia Very), Cinderella, and King Winter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An 1868 Prang catalogue would later claim that such “books in the shape of a regular paper Doll… originated with us”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It would seem the claim could also extend to die cut books in general, as we can’t find anything sooner, but do let us know in the comments if you have further light to shed on this! Such books are, of course, still popular in children’s publishing today, though the die cutting is not now limited to mere outlines, as evidenced in a beautiful 2014 version of the same Little Red Riding Hood story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The die cut has also been employed in the non-juvenile sphere as well, a recent example being Jonathan Safran Foer’s ambitious Tree of Codes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for this particular rendition of Charles Perrault’s classic tale, the text and design is by Lydia Very (1823-1901), sister of Transcendentalist poet Jones Very. The gruesome ending of the original — which sees Little Red Riding Hood being gobbled up as well as her grandmother — is avoided here, the gore giving way to the less bloody aims of the morality tale, and the lesson that one should not disobey one’s mother.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/red-riding.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/mediumish-theme-jekyll/jekyll/tutorial/2018/01/12/red-riding.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Jekyll</category>
        
        <category>tutorial</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
